<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Baylee Cheung on Baylee Cheung</title>
    <link>b4yc.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi, I&#39;m Baylee Cheung on Baylee Cheung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:42:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="b4yc.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>b4yc.github.io/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 12:26:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>b4yc.github.io/skills/</guid>
      <description>hello</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>b4yc.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:01:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>b4yc.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Relectric Car Team At Relectric, our goal is dedicated to accelerating the advancement of sustainable transport, while making this technology more accessible. At this team, I am the User Interface sub-team lead and I lead a group into creating a fully functioning user interface to implement into the car. This includes both the dashboard system and the infotainment system. From displaying vital information about the vehicle to playing music to make the ride more enjoyable, we are responsible for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>b4yc.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:55:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>b4yc.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;d love to get in touch with you! Send me an email</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>b4yc.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:49:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>b4yc.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Baylee Cheung and I am currently a third year Software Engineering student pursuing a minor in Biomedical Engineering. I am a driven student at the University of Calgary aspiring to make a positive impact in this world through technology. I love using creative approaches to find innovative solutions, and I believe software is the perfect medium for unlimited potential. I am passionate about streamlining the interaction between humans and technology and I am constantly learning new things everyday in order to achieve my goals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>